[
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the melee battle instructor?",
        "options": ["Arthur", "Nathalia", "Norah", "Valerius"],
        "correctAnswer": "Norah"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the element that manipulates plants?",
        "options": ["Earth", "Veggie", "Plant", "Life"],
        "correctAnswer": "Life"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hit Valerius in the first exam?",
        "options": ["Peter", "Julius", "Grim", "None of the above"],
        "correctAnswer": "Peter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why didn't Sarah win her battle against Victor?",
        "options": ["He landed a wind blow in her", "Victor punched her with an ice gauntlet", "She ran out of energy", "He froze her and then pushed her out from the battlefield"],
        "correctAnswer": "She ran out of energy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are Peter's dorm neighbors?",
        "options": ["Arnold and Kray", "Arthur and Paul", "Paul and Victor", "Victor and Kray"],
        "correctAnswer": "Victor and Kray"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the element that manipulates time?",
        "options": ["Clock", "Chrono", "Time", "Development"],
        "correctAnswer": "Development"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the academy?",
        "options": ["Mayhem", "Maysem", "Marsh", "Mhaysem"],
        "correctAnswer": "Maysem"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the director of the school?",
        "options": ["Nathalia Marklight", "May Marklight", "Valerius", "Stanley Griffinoir"],
        "correctAnswer": "Nathalia Marklight"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the creature that attacked the city in the first chapter?",
        "options": ["A lightning dragon", "A giant flying marten", "A fire leopard", "A giant golem"],
        "correctAnswer": "A lightning dragon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the city Peter lives?",
        "options": ["Lagoon City", "Light City", "Red City", "Fire City"],
        "correctAnswer": "Lagoon City"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character that can manipulate ice?",
        "options": ["Victor", "Paul", "Kray", "Julius"],
        "correctAnswer": "Victor"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character that can manipulate wind?",
        "options": ["Julius", "Kray", "Victor", "Arnold"],
        "correctAnswer": "Victor"
    }
]